"use strict"; //what is this?
class Game {
  constructor() {
    this.gameIsOver = false;
    this.score = 0; //if score.length === 6, WINNER - enter the club
    this.incorrectAnswer = 0; //if incorrectanswer.length === 1, this.lives -1
    this.totalIncorrect = 0; //if totalincorrect.length === 2, GAME OVER
    this.lives = 2;
    this.isWinner = false;
    this.questions = [...this.myCards];
    this.answeredQst = [];

    /*this.progressBar = 0;
    this.timer = 0;*/
  }

  getRandomCard() {
    //eventually will return RANDOM q, not first index
    let currentQIndx = Math.floor(Math.random() * this.questions.length);
    let currentQst = this.questions[currentQIndx];
    this.answeredQst.push(currentQst);
    this.questions.splice(currentQIndx, 1);

    console.log("question number", this.questions);
    console.log("answered qst", this.answeredQst);

    return currentQst;
  }

  scoreUp() {
    this.score += 1;
  }

  /*resetScore(){ 
  this.score = 0
}*/

  takeLife() {
    this.lives -= 1;
  }

  

  myCards = [
    {
      question: "Where was Techno music first pioneered?",
      answers: ["Ibiza, Spain", "New York, USA", "London, UK", "Detroit, USA"],
      correctAnswer: "Detroit, USA", // also can gove the index of the correct answer
    },

    {
      question: "In which era was Techno music developed in?",
      answers: ["1990s", "2010s", "1980s", "2000s"],
      correctAnswer: "1980s",
    },
    {
      question:
        "In which location was the now closed, world-famous nightclub Space?",
      answers: ["Miami", "Ibiza", "Mallorca", "Manchester"],
      correctAnswer: "Ibiza",
    },
    {
      question: "Who composed the famous techno track 'The Bells'?",
      answers: ["Jeff Mills", "Carl Cox", "Amelie Lens", "Laurent Garnier"],
      correctAnswer: "Jeff Mills",
    },
    {
      question: "In which country is Sunwaves Festival held twice a year?",
      answers: ["Italy", "China", "Romania", "Fiji"],
      correctAnswer: "Romania",
    },
    {
      question: "Barcelona is home to which of these famous techno DJs?",
      answers: [
        "Dubfire, Maceo Plex, Marco Carola",
        "Peggy Gou, Green Velvet, Sven VÃ¤th",
        "Deborah de Luca, Adam Beyer, Chris Liebing",
        "Ben Klock, Marco Carola, Joseph Capriati",
      ],
      correctAnswer: "Dubfire, Maceo Plex, Marco Carola",
    },
    {
      question: "Who is often considered 'The Father of Techno'?",
      answers: [
        "Marco Santonastasi",
        "Enrique Iglesias",
        "Juan Atkins",
        "Derrick May",
      ],
      correctAnswer: "Juan Atkins",
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the most utilized instrument by original techno producers?",
      answers: ["TR-808", "SH-101", "TB-303", "NI-909"],
      correctAnswer: "TR-808",
    },
    {
      question: "In which country is Timewarp Festival held every April?",
      answers: ["Germany", "France", "Scotland", "Portugal"],
      correctAnswer: "Germany",
    },
    {
      question: "Which of these DJs is a regular resident at Berghain?",
      answers: ["David Guetta", "Ben Klock", "Locomia", "Oxia"],
      correctAnswer: "Ben Klock",
    },
  ];
}
